<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="new_release_body">
        <item>Users can provide data voluntarily to help improve the #OstaniZdrav app further and help experts evaluate its effectiveness. It is not possible to draw any conclusions about individual persons, so that the privacy of the users is protected.</item>
        <item>Certificates can now be moved to the Trash when deleted, where they will remain stored for 30 days. During this time you can also restore them.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_linkified_labels">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_target_urls">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_title">
        <item>Privacy preserving analytics</item>
        <item>Trash and certificate recovery</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submission_done_further_info_bullet_points">
        <item>The duration of isolation is at the discretion of your treating physician.</item>
        <item>In case of worsening of the disease, consult your chosen personal or on-duty doctor by phone. In an emergency, call 112. Inform them that you have been diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2.</item>
        <item>Exposure logging has stopped because you have been diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2 infection. When the isolation is finished, press the Reactivate button and the exposure log will be activated.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submission_symptom_symptom_bullets">
        <item>Feeling unwell</item>
        <item>Cold signs</item>
        <item>Cough</item>
        <item>Fever</item>
        <item>Shortness of breath</item>
        <item>Headache</item>
        <item>Muscle pains</item>
        <item>Loss of smell ortaste</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="test_result_card_negative_further_info_bullet_points">
        <item>Still feeling unwell? If you feel very poorly and/or your symptoms have worsened, please contact your general practitioner.</item>
        <item>Remain at home until you feel well again. If you were to get infected with coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) whilst weakened from another infection, this could lead to a serious illness.</item>
        <item>Do not go to work if you feel unwell to ensure you do not put other people at risk.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
