<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="new_release_body">
        <item>Add your EU digital COVID certificates to the application. In this way, you will be able to prove that you meet the PCT conditions using the application.</item>
        <item>You can now add digital COVID certificates of family members in the app.</item>
        <item>You can now verify the validity of certificates for a selected country before you travel.</item>
        <item>\#OstaniZdrav offers you to check-in at events. Event organizers and store owners can generate a QR code with the app. Visitors can then scan this QR code upon arrival and save a check-in in the app. The application can also create an entry in contact journal on request. If someone who attends this event is later diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2, others who were present at the event at the same time may be alerted.</item>
        <item>For quick access to the QR code scanner, it has been added to the toolbar. With it, you can scan a QR code at an event or a COVID certificate. It also allows you to import QR codes from a file or photo.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_linkified_labels">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_target_urls">
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="new_release_title">
        <item>EU digital COVID certificates</item>
        <item>Family Certificates</item>
        <item>EU Certificate Validation</item>
        <item>Check-in at events</item>
        <item>QR code Scanner</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submission_done_further_info_bullet_points">
        <item>The duration of isolation is at the discretion of your treating physician.</item>
        <item>In case of worsening of the disease, consult your chosen personal or on-duty doctor by phone. In an emergency, call 112. Inform them that you have been diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2.</item>
        <item>Exposure logging has stopped because you have been diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2 infection. When the isolation is finished, press the Reactivate button and the exposure log will be activated.</item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submission_intro_bullet_points">
        <item>If you have been diagnosed with SARS-CoV-2 infection, you can inform others by entering the TAN code. You received the TAN code via SMS.</item>
        <item>If you have not yet received the TAN code or it has expired, you can obtain it via the online form in the next step.</item>
        <item></item>
        <item></item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="submission_symptom_symptom_bullets">
        <item>Feeling unwell</item>
        <item>Cold signs</item>
        <item>Cough</item>
        <item>Fever</item>
        <item>Shortness of breath</item>
        <item>Headache</item>
        <item>Muscle pains</item>
        <item>Loss of smell ortaste</item>
        <item>Sore throat</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="test_result_card_negative_further_info_bullet_points">
        <item>Still feeling unwell? If you feel very poorly and/or your symptoms have worsened, please contact your general practitioner.</item>
        <item>Remain at home until you feel well again. If you were to get infected with coronavirus (SARS-CoV-2) whilst weakened from another infection, this could lead to a serious illness.</item>
        <item>Do not go to work if you feel unwell to ensure you do not put other people at risk.</item>
        <item>If your symptoms worsen, you might need another SARS-CoV-2 test.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
